now it's your turn let's do a quiz on
right back caches suppose we have a
direct map cache and this is one entry
in that cache and all of the accesses we
will do will map to that one entry the
valid bit starts out at zero the dirty
bit starts out at one and the tag starts
out at a the processor does the
following sequence of accesses it reads
a reads be writes be read C reads the
writes D and all of these ABC and D map
to the same place in the cache the
question for you is after these accesses
what is the new state of the cache also
you need to determine how many cache
misses do we have in this sequence of
accesses and how many write backs to
memory will happen during this sequence